Register to the Papers of Vladimir and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz
Yale University Music Library
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1890-1991; Series I; 32 boxes (13.3')
  - CORRESPONDENCE - Personal, I.A
    - Raymont, Henry S.
      See: New York Times
    - Rayner, John P.
      See: Marquette University
    - Rayward, Tamara, 1986 May 5; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 170)
    - Razzi, Giulio
      See: RAI
    - Reader's Digest, 1978 May-Nov.; 12 items. (Box 13, Folder 171)
      Includes 2 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 3 enclosures.
      See also: Gregory, Paul
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1986-1989; 15 items. (Box 13, Folder 172)
      Includes Vladimir Horowitz and Wanda Horowitz reply and enclosure
    - Recital Stage Inc., 1972 Sep. 27; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Recording for the Blind, Inc., 1980 Mar. 28; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Rector, Gail W., 1978-1986; 9 items. (Box 13, Folder 173)
      See also: University of Michigan. University Musical Society
    - Regional Arts Productions, Inc., 1977 Feb. 10; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Reh, Hollis, ca. 1989 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Reinarz, Mariëtte, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Reinhardt, Gottfried, 1965-1982; 3 items. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Reisenberg, Nadia, 1976 July 26; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Reisseman, Oskar von, 1934 Sep. 21; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Relatively Speaking, 1988 Sep. 2-14; 3 items. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Repubblica, 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Respighi, Ottorino and Elsa, 1933 Nov.-Dec.; 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Réunion des Théâtres Lyriques Nationaux, 1969 Jan. 21; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Revenaugh, Daniell, 1982 Aug. 1; 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Revezzoni, Carla, 1989 Nov. 9; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Rexall Drugs
      See: Mond, Phyliss and Bert
    - Rhodes, Rosalee and Arthur?, 1989 Nov. 24; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Ribicoff, Casey (Mrs. Abraham), 1985 July-Aug.; 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Richmond, Aaron, 1953-1968; 5 items. (Box 13, Folder 174)
      See also: Pierce, Walter
    - Richmond, Anne (Mrs. Aaron), 1968 Sep. 24; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Richter, Bob, 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Richter, Sviatoslav, 1965 May 8; 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Ricordi, Giulia Ponti, 1989 Nov. 6; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Riemann Musiklexikon, 1970 Feb.-July; 8 items. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Rignano, Guido, 1989 Nov. 9; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Rimini, Rosa Raisa, ca. 1933 Dec.; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Rizzoli Center, ca. 1967 Apr. 4; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Rizzoli Corporation, 1967 July 25; 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Roberts, Allen, 1970 Apr.-Aug.; 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Robinor, Genia, 1965 May 29; 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Robinson, Francis, 1967-1968; 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Robson, John Fiske, 1968-1990; 28 items. (Box 13, Folder 175)
      9 enclosures, 1 oversize
    - [Rock-Savage, Lord] David, 1986-1990; 3 items. (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1971-1978; 3 items. (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - Roderman, Nick, Mary, Gilbert, and Anna Marie, 1984-1989; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Rodzinski, Halina (Mrs. Arthur) and Riki, 1965-1989; 6 items. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Rogoff, Ilan, 1966 Dec. 25; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Romanoff, Nikita and Janet, ca. 1989 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Romon, Josef, 1949 Jan. 9; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Roos, James
      See: Miami Herald
    - Roosevelt, Anna, 1965 Nov. 12; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Roos-Moesker, M.H., 1989 Nov. 6; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Rosa Ponselle Museum, 1984 Oct. 10-26; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 176)
      See also: Ponselle, Rosa
    - Rosenbluth, Darrell, 1989 Nov. 5; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Rosenstein, Gertrude, 1989 Nov. 9; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Rosenthal, Barbara and Sidney, 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Rosenthal, Jesse S., M.D., Robin, and Joshua, 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Ross, Sidney, 1986-1989; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Ross, Lillian and Sidney, 1965-1968; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Rossi, Enrica Pellegrini, 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Rostropovich, Mstislav, 1980 May-June; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 176)
    - Roth, E. (John) and Gene, 1960-1965; 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 177)
    - Rothe, Friede F., 1965-1968; 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 177)
    - Rother, Eve, 1979-1988; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 177)
    - Rothschild, Elie de, 1986-1990; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 177)
    - Royal, John F., 1965-1968; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 177)
    - Royal Philharmonic Society, 1969-1974; 32 items. (Box 14, Folder 178)
      Includes 9 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 2 enclosures.
      See also: Foggin, Myers
    - Rubin, Cyma? (Mrs. Samuel), ca. 1965 May; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 179)
    - Rubin, David W. and Vivian, 1951-1988; 31 items. (Box 14, Folder 179)
      See also: Cooper, Peter; Davis, Richard B.; Ito, Akihiko; and Steinway & Sons
    - Rubinstein, Arthur and Nela, 1956-1978; 7 items. (Box 14, Folder 180)
    - Rubinstein, Leslie, 1985 June 9; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - Rubstein, Ariel, 1965 May 9-25; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - Rudolf, Anthony, 1982 May 17; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - Ruggeri, R., 1933 Dec. 4; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - Rush, Susan and Mollie Russell, Peter, 1988; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - Russian Life Daily, ca. 1986 Sep. 8; 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - Rutgers University, 1966 May 10; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - S. Feldman Inc., ca. 1989 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - Saal, Hubert, n.y. May 6; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - Sachs, Harvey, 1988-1989; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - Sager, Christopher Czaja, 1986 Nov. 3; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - Saidenberg, Daniel, 1965 May 21-27; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - Saikali, Niphon, ca. 1986; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - St. Andrew Catholic Church, 1989 Aug. 14; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - Saint Anthony of Padua Church, 1988 Dec. 25; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - St. James Community House (Box 14, Folder 183)
      See: Maynor, Dorothy
    - St. Patrick's College, 1969 Jan.-Mar.; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - St. Stephen United Methodist Church, 1981 July 6; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - Saint-Tropez
      See: Lescudier, Jean
    - Saitzoff, Nata (Mrs. Alexander, 1938-1988; 10 items. (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - Sak's Fifth Avenue, ca. 1990 Jan. 4; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - Sala Cecília Meireles - Funterj, 1976 Dec. 20; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - Salta in Bocca Restaurant
      See: Tramontino, Fulvio and Elide
    - Salman, Mark, 1988 Dec.; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - Samuel, Harold E.
      See: Yale Univerity. Music Library
    - Samuel, Paul, 1966 Apr.-May; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 184)
    - Sanders, Martijn, 1986-1989; 19 items. (Box 14, Folder 184)
      Includes 5 Vladimir Horowitz replies.
      See also: Concertgebouw
    - Sarnoff, Anna Moffo and Roberto, ca. 1989 Nov. 8; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 184)
    - Sarteschi, Carlo, 1933 Nov. 25; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 184)
    - Sasaki, Tadatsugu, 1971-1976; 6 items. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Saturday Evening Post
      See: Wagner, Jeanette Sarkisian
    - Saunder, Remi, 1965-1968; 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Saunders, Roger A., ca. 1986 Oct. 19; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Sava, Iosif, 1970 Apr. 22; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Save Our Strays, 1979-1980; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Schaeffer, Edith, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Schaffner, Mort, 1986 Nov. 8; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Schapiro, Ivor and Dorothy, 1989 Nov. 6; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Scheps, Frida, 1968 Jan. 9-24; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Schiffmann, David, 1969 Mar. 14; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Schillinger, Frances (Mrs. Joseph), 1967 Feb. 14; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Schirmer
    - Schleifer, Miriam (Mrs. Arthur), ca. 1969 Mar. 3; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Schlote, Hans, 1975 Jan. 21; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 186)
      Typed letter from Vladimir Horowitz to Shaw to reply
    - Schmid, Leo, 1987 May 30; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schmidt-Neuhaus, Astrid, 1980 Nov. 21; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schneider, Alexander (Sasha), 1965 Oct. 18; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schneider, Audrey and Laurence, 1988 Oct. 1; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schneider, Edouard, 1938 July 26; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schneider, Iris, 1977 Nov. 1-10; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Scholler, Gisela, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schonberg, Harold C., 1961-1991; 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schreiber, Edward, [1965] Apr. 1; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schubert Club, 1978 Feb. 2; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schuller, Robert Harold, 1986-1989; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schulman, Edwin L., 1989 Nov. 13; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schwann, William, 1974 July 3-12; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Schwartz, Bill, ca. 1989 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 187)
    - Schweizer, Heinrich, 1978 Feb.-Sep.; 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 187)
    - Sciullo, John M. and Ann, 1988-1991; 7 items. (Box 14, Folder 187)
    - Scotti, Gallarati, ca. 1933 Dec.; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 187)
    - Sea World Research Institute, 1989 July-Aug.; 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - Seagram Classics Wine Company
      See: Mumm Champagne
    - Seaman, ?, [1965] July 16; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - Seligmann, Arthur, M.D., and Betty, 1965 June 4-16; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - Serkin, Irene (Mrs. Rudolf), 1973-1990; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 189)
    - Serkin, Peter, 1975-1989; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 189)
    - Serkin, Rudolf and Irene, 1933-1989; 35 items. (Box 14, Folder 189-190)
    - Servizio Nazionale Lions Cani Guida per Ciechi, 1989 Nov. 10; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Seward, William, 1965 July 9; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Seward, William W., Jr., 1984 Mar. 12-16; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Shaborkina, Tat'iana Grigor'evna, 1976 Nov. 19; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Shalit, Gene, 1976-1977; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 191)
      Photograph enclosed
    - Shapiro, Alma and John, 1965 July 1; 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Shapiro, William M., 1970-1978; 21 items. (Box 14, Folder 191)
      Includes 2 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 17 enclosures
    - Shapiro, Yehuda
    - Sharon Hospital, Inc., 1979-1980; 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Shaw, Harold, 1975-1989; 36 items. (Box 14, Folder 192)
      Includes 8 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 2 enclosures.
      See also: Chapin, Schuyler G.; Freese, Arthur S.; Gingerich, John; Gregory, Paul; Hindell, Leonard; International Piano Competition (Japan); Maazel, Lorin; Palmer, Joye; United Kingdom. Embassy (U.S.); and I.B. Shaw Concerts.
    - [Shear], Nancy, 1991 June 28; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 193)
    - Sheehy, Michael, M.D., 1989 Nov. 8; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 193)
    - Shehori, Mordecai, 1988-1990; 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 193)
    - Shepard, Thomas Z., 1972-1989; 11 items. (Box 14, Folder 193)
      See also: CBS Records, MCA Records, RCA Records; and I.B. CBS Records
    - Sherman, Elliott and Claire, 1965 Apr. 28; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 193)
    - Sherry, Lee U., Dr., and Bernice, 1965-1989; 10 items. (Box 14, Folder 193)
      Includes Vladimir Horowitz reply and note.
      See also: Brandeis University Library Book Fund
    - Shih-tang, Hsu, 1978 Feb. 27; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Shohet, Valentine and Saleh, 1989 Nov. 6; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Shostakovich, Dmitri Dmitrievich, 1957-1965; 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Shultz, George, ca. 1987 Dec. 22; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Sieber, Rudi and Dietrich, Marlene
      See: Dietrich, Marlene
    - Siegel, Jeffrey, 1967-1988; 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Silber, John R.
      See: Wallace, Mike
    - Silverman, Fred, 1979 June 1; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Silverman, Robert J.
      See: Piano Quarterly
    - Simionato, Giulietta, 1989-1990; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Simon, Abbey, 1965-1970; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Simon, Jacqueline (Mrs. Pierre), 1965 May-June; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Simonilli, Maria and Bruno, 1989 Nov. 8; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Sinestrari, Carlo, ca. 1984 Oct. 1; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Sinigaglia, Leone, 1933 Oct. 5-6; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Sinzheimer, Max, 1973-1974; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Sirmay, Albert, 1953 Jan. 12; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Skolovsky, Zadel, 1965-1989; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Skouras, Dimitri, 1977 Mar. 2; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Skouras, Johanna, 1975-1976; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Skriabin Museum
      See: Shaborkina, Tat'iana Grigor'evna
    - Slezak, Walter and Johanna, 1957 Jan. 17; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Sloane, Robert B., D.D.S., 1978 Sep. 25; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Slonimsky, Nicolas, 1966 Oct.-Nov.; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 195)
      Includes Typed letter (copy) and reply from Wanda Toscanini Horowitz
    - Smetona, Vytautas, 1977-1979; 6 items. (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Smit, Leo, 1986 Oct. 29; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Smith, Arrietta H., 1965 June 24; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Smith, Clifford, 1974-1976; 13 items. (Box 15, Folder 196)
      10 enclosures
    - Smith, Ileene, 1986-1989; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Smith, Pamela, 1989 Nov. 8; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Smolenskii?, n.d.; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Smuzikov, Mikhail Abramovich, 1986 Apr. 18; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Smyth, Harriet R., 1986-1989; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Snowden, Lord
      See: Foyle, Christina
    - Società del Quartetto di Milano, 1987 Jan. 20; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Sofronitskaya, Yelena, 1976 Feb.-Mar.; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 197)
      See also: Cogan, Roxanne
    - Sogny, Michel, 1978 May-July; 6 items. (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Sohval, Arthur R., M.D., 1966 Apr. 4-6; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Solomon, Sonia, ca. 1988 Oct. 1; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Solow, Helena (Mrs. Leo), 1965 May-June; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Solti, Georg, 1989 Nov. 6; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Sony Classical Productions Inc., 1989-1990; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Sony Corporation of America, 1989 Nov. 16; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Sorel, Claudette, 1972-1975; 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Soria, Dario and Dorle, 1965-1989; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Sousa, John Philip, III, 1952 Feb. 4; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 198)
      Copy
    - South Aquebogue Company, 1979 Dec. 17; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Souvaine, Geraldine (Gerri), 1965 May 9-29; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Soviet Union. Ministerstvo Kultury
      See: Gribanov, Mikhail
    - Sovietskaia muzyka
      See: Edel'man, Georgii; and Iuzefovich, Viktor Aronovich
    - Soyer, David, 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Spence-Chapin, 1976 Sep. 20-22; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Sperandeo, Salvatore Duccio, 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Spiro, Lola (Mrs. Bob), 1966 Apr. 5; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Spivakov, Vladimir, 1986 Apr. 20; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Sporn, Henry, 1968 Jan.-Feb.; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Staierskii?, P.S., 1933 Sep. 22; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 199)
      Signed by several others. Enclosure.
    - Stamas, Stephen
    - Stangland, Thomas C., 1979 Aug. 6; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Steger, Jörg, 1980 Nov. 6; 6 items. (Box 15, Folder 199)
      5 photos enclosed
    - Stein, Beatrice Klug and Harry, 1977-1989; 13 items. (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Steinberg, William and Lotti, 1965 May-June; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Steiner, Christian, 1989 Dec. 20; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Steinert, Alec (Alinka), 1953 Jan. 12; 5 items. (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Steinfirst, Jane and Donald, 1953 Jan. 12; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Steinway, Frederick, 1965 May 9-24; 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Steinway, Henry Z., 1968-1991; 8 items. (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Steinway, John H., 1968-1982; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Steinway, Julia, ca. 1957 Jan.; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Steinway, Polly (Mrs. Henry Z.), n.d.; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Steinway, Ruth (Mrs. Theodore E.), 1965-[1968]; 5 items. (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Steinway, Theodore E., 1933-1957; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Steinway, William R., 1933-1957; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Steinway & Sons, 1957-1992; 20 items. (Box 15, Folder 200)
      See also: Bulva, Joseph, Davis, Richard B., Goodrich, Peter G.; Greiner, A.W.; Günther, Walther; Hupfer, Bill; Ito, Akihiko; Probst, Richard; [Shear], Nancy; individual Steinways; I.B. CBS TV show; and VI.C. Steinway
    - Steinway Musical Properties, 1987 Jan. 6; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Stern, Anne Bigelow (Mrs. Carl)
      See: Musicians Foundation
    - Stern, Isaac and Vera, 1965-1989; 11 items. (Box 15, Folder 201)
      See also: Carnegie Hall Corporation
    - Stern, Oscar, 1965 May-June; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - Stern, Rosalie M., 1939 Dec. 4-15; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - Stevens, Risë (Mrs. Walter Surovy), 1965-1986; 22 items. (Box 15, Folder 203)
      Includes 7 Vladimir Horowitz replies and an enclosure.
      See also: Mannes College of Music
    - Stewart, Natacha, 1965-1978; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Stichting Collectieve Grammofoon-platen Campagne, 1969 Oct.-Nov.; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Stierlin-Vallon, ?, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Stillman, Edgar, 1968 Oct. 3; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Stillman, Joan, n.y. Sep. 26; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Stillwaggon, Carol A., ca. 1989 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Stillwaggon, Gene, ca. 1989 Nov. 8; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Stockman, Russell M., 1991 Feb. 4; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Stojowska, Luisa M., 1951 Aug. 24; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Stokowski, Leopold, 1965-1969; 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Stonehouse, Brian, ca. 1965 May; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Strakach?, Syltvin?, 1930 or 1935? Dec. 14; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
      To Aleksandr Vladimirovich
    - Stralem, Jean (Mrs. Donald S.), 1969-1989; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Straram, Enrich, 1957 Jan. 17; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Stravinsky, Soulima, 1969 Sep. 23; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Stricker, Mrs. William, ca. 1989 Dec. 11; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Strickland, Daniel, 1965 June 17; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Stroumillo, Choura, 1968 Sep. 23; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Stroumillo, Olga, 1968-1987; 16 items. (Box 15, Folder 205)
      Vladimir Horowitz reply and 6 enclosures.
    - Strunk, Pamela, ca. 1965 May; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Sturani, Cesare (Cesarino), 1957-1965; 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Sultanov, Alexei, 1990 Mar. 22; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Sunday Times, 1978 Aug. 4; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Surovy, Risë Stevens
      See: Stevens, Risë (Mrs. Walter Surovy)
    - Swedish Clementi Association
      See: Hultman, Anders
    - Sweeney, Louise, n.d.; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Swet, Gershon, 1949 Jan. 6; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Sylvania Service Company, Inc., 1968; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Sylvester, Ralph, 1989 Aug. 7; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Symphonicum Europae Ste Cle, 1977 Sep. 21; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Szanto, Jani
      See: Fiorillo, Alexander
    - S., Ali, 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - TADC, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Tamiroff, Akim and Tamara, 1953-1965; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Taplin, Frank E., 1978 Mar. 1; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Tarafa, Fifi, 1965 May-June; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Tarasov, Lev Mikhailovich
      See: Konstantinova, Irina Georgievna
    - Tarnowsky, Sergei and Maxine, 1965-1967; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 206)
      See: Podolsky, Lee
    - Taub, Robert, 1981-1983; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Taubman, Howard, 1952-1989; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 206)
      Includes typescript of interview
    - Taulbee, Mr. and Mrs. Jack, 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, ca. 1986 Apr.; 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 206)
      Note and translation by Suzanne Fusso, 'Note from Vladimir Horowitz to Pëtr Il'ich Chaikovskii (along with card "To Pëtr Il'ich Chaikovskii - At the cemetary in Leningrad"'
      Includes 2 copies of note to "Petia" and his family
    - Teatro alla Scala
      See also: Badini, Carlo Maria; Escobar, Sergio; and Grassi, Paolo
    - Tebet, David, 1978 Sep. 21-28; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Telrad Electronics, 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Thannhauser, Justin K. and Hilde, 1965 June 2; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Theatre de Champs Elysees
      See: Hirsch, Georges François
    - Theodoli, Maria and Dandolo, 1986-1989; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Thode, Daniela (Mrs. Freii von Bülow), 1932-1938; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Thompson, Thomas, 1965-1967; 7 items. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Threadgill, Francis, 1967 Sep. 7; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Tilney, Guinevere and John, 1989 Nov. 11; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Time
      See: Kanfer, Stefan
    - Tishman, Rita, 1965 June 17; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Toeplitz, Rysia Consolo, ca. 1989 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Tognoli, Carlo, 1985 Nov. 9; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Toho-Geino Corporation
    - Tolstoy, Alexandra, 1960-1968; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Tommasini, Vincenzo?, 1933 Oct. 10; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Toscanini, Arturo / Arturo Toscanini to family, 1926-1949; 9 items. (Box 15, Folder 208)
      From Arturo Toscanini to Carla Toscanini 5 envelopes laid in
    - Toscanini, Arturo / Arturo Toscanini to family, 1916-1956; 26 items. (Box 15, Folder 209)
      From Arturo Toscanini to Wanda Toscanini Horowitz 10 envelopes laid in, 1 without a letter, and 1 note on envelope decorated with ribbon by Arturo Toscanini
    - Toscanini, Arturo / Arturo Toscanini to family, 1936-1955; 5 items. (Box 16, Folder 210)
      From Arturo Toscanini to Vladimir Horowitz
      Note on back of undated letter from "Emanuele"
      Includes an envelope without a letter, and an arrangement of song by Arturo Toscanini for Vladimir Horowitz's birthday: [Happy birthday to you; arr.] [Happy birthday to you] / [arranged by Arturo Toscanini], ca. 1947 October 1.
      [1] sheet of music; 28 cm.
      Holograph in ink [red and blue].
      Inscription: "A Valodia October 1 1947"
      On stationery with Arturo Toscanini's letterhead.
    - Toscanini, Arturo / Arturo Toscanini to family, 1940-1951; 16 items. (Box 16, Folder 211-212)
      From Arturo Toscanini to Sonia Horowitz
      Includes 5 photographs, 5 envelopes with letters, and 3 without letters, and 2 songs by Arturo Toscanini for Sonia Horowitz
      [2] p.; 37 cm. Holograph signed, in ink
      Inscription on title page: "To Sonia Horowitz from Beethoven's substitute". Words on title page: "Sonia don't forget your nonno, send him quick your composition, otherwise he will lose Riverdale -- Buenos Aires. 29 Giugno 1941"
      [2] p.; 24 x 29 cm. Holograph in ink. Same inscription and words on title page as above. Envelope laid in.